Guide to the Atlanta Lesbian Feminist Alliance Periodicals Collection, 1962-1994 RL.00024
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Atlanta Lesbian Feminist Alliance (ALFA) Periodicals collection
1962-1994
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Atlanta Lesbian Feminist Alliance
RL.00024
70.5 Linear Feet
The Atlanta Lesbian Feminist Alliance (ALFA) was a grassroots lesbian feminist activist organization founded in 1972 and disbanded in 1994. The ALFA Periodicals Collection, dated 1962-1994, contains over 800 grassroots newsletter and journal titles from feminist, LGBT, and other activist groups primarily located in the Southeast but also including titles from around the U.S. and abroad. Many of the titles are now ephemeral and not found in any library. The collection was originally established and maintained as part of the Atlanta Lesbian Feminist Alliance's library and archives. Also included are non-regional women's and lesbian journals from the early women's movement as well as some long runs of gay newspapers published throughout the U.S. and Canada.
About 33,750 Items
Microfilm Available
The majority of titles in the collection are also available on microfilm.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Atlanta Lesbian Feminist Alliance Periodicals Collection was received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a purchase in 1994.
Historical Note
The Atlanta Lesbian Feminist Alliance (ALFA) was founded in 1972 by a group of radical lesbians, many socialist and all feminist, who broke away from Atlanta's Women's Liberation Center and the Gay Liberation movement because they felt that neither had adequately addressed issues of concern to women as lesbians and lesbians as women. ALFA initially worked to fill a social void for and to offer a political voice to Atlanta lesbians, publicizing its efforts through a self-produced monthly newsletter, the Atalanta.
Over the years, as the political and cultural climate changed and lesbians created new avenues through which to pursue their interests, ALFA struggled to find a clear and unique sense of purpose; this historically telling struggle is well-documented by ALFA itself, in minutes and mailings to its membership. In spite of its eventual decision to disband, ALFA remains known as one of the oldest lesbian feminist organizations in the United States, and a pioneer in the fight for lesbian, gay, and women's rights.
One of the activities of ALFA--deeply concerned from the outset with the preservation of lesbian "herstory"--was to build and maintain the Southern Feminist Library and Archives (SFLA). The library and archives, which provided a material link between ALFA and other progressive movements and organizations throughout the world, included the archival records of ALFA and several other southern feminist groups; a massive collection of feminist, lesbian, and activist periodicals; and a circulating library of feminist and gay and lesbian books. ALFA disbanded in 1994 after over 20 years of Southern feminist activism. Acquired as part of the Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture.
Collection Overview
The ALFA Periodicals Collection, dated 1962-1994, contains over 800 grassroots newsletter and journal titles, many of which are now ephemeral and not in any library. The publications were collected by ALFA generally by means of exchange subscriptions with other lesbian, feminist, and activist groups from all over the U.S. and abroad. The periodicals cover a range of topics of interest and concern to socialist lesbian feminists. In addition to strictly lesbian and feminist publications, there is a wealth of publications from other leftist activist groups covering political and social causes from anti-nuclear weapons, to AIDS activism, to the beginnings of the men's movement. The collection helps document these various political movements as well as the issues facing the people whose task it was to document them.
Collection Arrangement
Arranged alphabetically by title.
Related Material
Atlanta Lesbian Feminist Alliance archives, 1972-1994
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University
Atlanta Lesbian Feminist Alliance financial papers, 1972-1994
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University
Atlanta Lesbian Feminist Alliance Archives [and Periodicals, ca. 1972-1994] [microform]
Duke University Libraries
Gay liberation movement -- United States -- Periodicals; Feminism -- Georgia -- Periodicals; Lesbianism -- United States -- Periodicals; Gay liberation movement -- Southern States -- Periodicals; Lesbians -- Southern States; Lesbianism -- Georgia -- Periodicals; Women -- Southern States; Feminism -- Southern States -- Societies, etc.; Gay activists -- Southern States; Lesbian activists -- United States; Lesbian activists -- Southern States; Women political activists -- United States; Atlanta Lesbian Feminist Alliance; Sallie Bingham Center for Women's History and Culture
- ALFA Periodicals Collection, 1972-1994, 47 boxes
  Arrangement note
  Arranged alphabetically by title.
  - AEGIS (Washington, D.C.), 1984 May (Box 1)
  - Affirmative (Los Angeles, Calif.), 1980 August (Box 1)
    Scope and Contents note
    Gay & Lesbian Mormons
  - After Stonewall (Canada), 1980 (Box 1)
    Critical Journal of Lesbian and Gay Liberation in [?], Canada
  - Agape (Tallahassee, Fla.), 1977 January-1977 December (Box 1)
    Alliance for Gay Awareness (Florida State University)
  - AID Atlanta Infolines Newsletter, 1991 January-1994 February (Box 1)
  - AID Atlanta, Journal of, 1985 December-1990 October (Box 1)
  - AID Atlanta Newsletter, 1983 August-1985 July (Box 1)
  - ACE News (Savannah, Ga.), 1988 September-1989 October (Box 1)
    AIDS Coastal Empire Foundation
  - AIDS Project-LA, 1987 March-1988 August (Box 1)
  - AIDS Survival Project, 1994 January-1994 March (Box 1)
  - AIDS Treatment News (San Francisco, Calif.), 1988 July (Box 1)
  - AIDS Walk Atlanta, 1992 August (Box 1)
  - Aid to Imprisoned Mothers (Atlanta, Ga.), 1988 April (Box 1)
  - Ain't I a Woman? (Iowa City, Iowa), 1970 July-1974 May [?] (Box 1)
  - Albatross (East Orange, N.J.), 1975 March-1976 (Box 1)
  - Albatross, The (Brewton, Ala.), 1984 August (Box 1)
  - Alive and Aware, 1987 November (Box 1)
  - Al-Raida (Beirut, Lebanon), 1981 October-1990 February [?] (Box 1)
    Beirut University College (Lebanon)
  - Alternate Roots (Atlanta, Ga.), 1987-1994 (Box 1)
  - Alternative to Alienation, 1976 March-1976 April (Box 1)
  - Amazing Grace, 1974 (Box 1)
  - Amazon: A Feminist Journal (Milwaukee, Wis.), 1975 May-1981 January [?] (Box 1)
  - Amazon Quarterly (West Somerville, Mass.), 1972-1975 (Box 1)
  - ACLU Women's Rights Report, 1981 February-February 1982 [?] (Box 2)
  - American Civil Liberties Union - Civil Liberties, 1975-1990 (Box 2)
    #308-#370 [missing 309, 317, 318, 330, 350, 352, 357, 358, 359]
  - American Civil Liberties Union of Georgia - Civil Liberties, 1973 October (Box 2)
  - American Medical Student Association News (AMSA News), 1986 January-1986 June (Box 2)
  - AMSA News: Lesbian, Gay, and Bisexual People in Medicine, 1985 June-1985 December (Box 2)
  - American Voice, The (Louisville, Ky.), 1990 (Box 2)
  - Amethyst (Atlanta, Ga.), 1988-1992 (Box 2)
    #3-#8 [missing 4, 5]
  - Among Friends (Madison, Wis.), 1986 April (Box 2)
  - Ample Information (Portland, Ore.), 1985 February-1985 December (Box 2)
    Also flier from 1986
  - Anamika - (Lesbian Indian Newsletter), 1985 May-1987 June (Box 2)
  - Animals Agenda, The, 1985 May (Box 2)
  - Annotated Guide to Women's Periodicals in the United States and Canada (Richmond, Ind.), 1982 February-1984 October (Box 2)
    Earlham College
  - Anti Draft Update: A Card, 1980 December (Box 2)
  - Antioch Record, The (Yellow Spring, Ohio), 1980-1981 (Box 2)
    Newspaper of Antioch College
  - Aphra (New York, N.Y.), 1969-1976 (Box 2)
    [Quarterly]
  - Aquelarre: Latin American Women's Cultural Society (Vancouver, British Columbia), 1990 October-1990 December (Box 2)
  - A.R.M Abortion Rights Movement of Women's Liberation (Washington, D.C.), 1979 July/August (Box 2)
  - ART Beat: Alternative Resources of the Triad Newsletter (Greensboro, N.C.), 1990 June (Box 2)
  - ART Workers News, 1974 May-1974 June (Box 2)
  - Asian Lesbians of the East Coast (Brooklyn, N.Y.), 1984 September [?] (Box 2)
  - Astrological Current Events (Atlanta, Ga.), 1989 July-1990 September (Box 2)
  - Athena, 1989 March (Box 2)
  - Athens Gay, The, 1984 November-1985 November (Box 2)
    Lesbian Allianced Newsletter
  - Atlanta Barb, circa 1973 (Box 3)
  - Atlanta Business and Professional Guild News, 1982 September-1985 May (Box 3)
  - Atlanta Business and Professional Guild Phoenix, 1985 December-1986 October (Box 3)
  - Atlanta Business and Professional Guild Newsletter, 1988 March-1984 June (Box 3)
  - Atlanta Center for Feminist Studies Quarterly (Atlanta, Ga.), 1985 December [?] (Box 3)
  - Atlanta Committee on Latin America (Atlanta, Ga.), 1983 November-1991 April (Box 3)
  - Atlanta Gay Center: The News, 1984-1994 [?] (Box 3)
  - Atlanta Gay Central (Atlanta, Ga.), 1979 April-1984 September (Box 3)
  - Atlanta Now, 1976 November-1986 December (Box 3)
  - Atlanta Report from Atlanta Clergy and Laity Concerned (Decatur, Ga.), 1979 November-1984 March (Box 3)
    [missing: 1980, 1981, 1983]
  - Atlanta Gay News (Atlanta, Ga.), 1978 June-1979 January (Box 3)
  - Atlanta Greens, 1994 March (Box 3)
  - Atlanta NAPWA, 1993 May-1993 December (Box 3)
  - Atlanta Women's Era (Decatur, Ga.), 1977 September-1978 June [?] (Box 3)
  - Atlantans Concerned for El Salvador, 1981 March (Box 4)
  - Augusta Gay Lesbian Contact (Augusta, Ga.), 1984 April-1986 November (Box 4)
  - Aunt Edna's Reading List (Honolulu, Hawaii), 1987 June-1989 November (Box 4)
  - Austin Dyke (Austin, Texas), 1979 October-1980 August [?] (Box 4)
  - Austin Lambda Newsletter (Austin, Texas), 1981 March-1982 January [?] (Box 4)
  - Awake & Move (Penllyn, Pa.), 1971 March (Box 4)
  - A Woman's Place (Atlanta, Ga.), 1981 September (Box 4)
  - Azalea: A Magazine by Third World (New York, N.Y.), 1978 (Box 4)
  - Backgrounds (Wilmington, N.C.), 1990 April-1990 September (Box 4)
    A newsletter from GROW, a Community Service Corp.
  - Bad Attitude (Boston, Mass.), 1984 (Box 4)
  - Baltimore Alternative, The, 1986 August (Box 4)
  - Bar None (West Somerville, Mass.), circa 1975-1977 (Box 4)
  - Bay Area Reporter, 1984 [?] (Box 4)
  - Belles Lettres: A Review of Books by Women, 1987 (Box 4)
  - Berdache, Le (Montreal, Quebec), 1982 May (Box 4)
  - Berliner Business Report, 1985 May (Box 4)
  - Bet Haverim (Atlanta, Ga.), 1985 October-1993 February (Box 4)
  - Between Our Selves (Washington, D.C.), 1985 (Box 4)
  - Between Ourselves (Wilmington, N.C.), 1990 March-1991 November (Box 4)
  - Big Apple Dyke News (Bad News) (New York, N.Y.), 1981-1986 (Box 4)
    [missing: 1983, 1985]
  - Big Mama Rag (Denver, Colo.), 1974 December-1984 April [?] (Box 4)
  - Bimonthly, The, 1983 May-1983 September (Box 5)
  - Binghamton Women's Center (Binghamton, N.Y.), 1984 November-1986 April (Box 5)
  - Bi Pol, 1984 April (Box 5)
  - Black and White Men Together / Atlanta, 1982 January-1994 March (Box 5)
  - Black Belt Woman (Medford, Mass.), 1975 September-1976 August (Box 5)
  - Black Forum, The (Los Angeles, Calif.), 1988 (Box 5)
  - Black Lesbian Newsletter (Berkeley, Calif.), 1983 March [?] (Box 5)
  - Black Maria (Chicago, Ill.), 1981 April [?] (Box 5)
  - Black Woman's Voice (New York, N.Y.), 1980 February [?] (Box 5)
  - Bodybuilding Women (New York, N.Y.), 1987 September-1989 February (Box 5)
  - Blade, The (Washington, D.C.), 1979 October-1979 November [?] (Box 5)
  - Blazing Star, 1975 May / 1979 May (Box 5)
    [missing: 1976, 1977, 1978]
  - BLK, 1983 December-1994 February [?] (Box 5)
  - The Body Politic: Gay Liberation Journal (Toronto, Ontario), 1971-1987 (Box 5-6)
  - Body Community Star, 1974 December-1992 June [?] (Box 7)
  - Boston Gay Review (Boston, Mass.), 1981 February (Box 7)
  - Bottomfish Blues, 1990 (Box 7)
  - Boulder Gay Record, 1974 April-1974 July (Box 7)
  - Boxcar, 1978 (Box 7)
  - Bridges: A Journal for Jewish Feminists and Our Friends, 1990 (Box 7)
  - Broadside (Toronto, Ontario), 1982 August [?] (Box 7)
  - Broomstick, 1986 January-1990 June (Box 7)
  - Brother (Berkeley, Calif.), 1974 (Box 7)
  - Bulletin (Montreal, Quebec), 1978 December (Box 7)
  - Calendar, The (Connecticut), 1988 August-1988 September (Box 7)
  - Calendar, The (San Antonio, Texas), 1983 May-1984 August (Box 7)
  - Calendar of Events - Jacksonville, FL, 1987 April-1989 February (Box 7)
  - Calling All Girls (Durham, N.C.), 1982 April (Box 7)
  - Callisto (Newsletter of the Women's Spirituality) (Berkeley, Calif.), 1990 (Box 7)
  - Campaign for a Prosperous Georgia: Plugging In (Atlanta, Ga.), 1987-1993 (Box 7)
  - Camping Women Trails (Sacramento, Calif.), 1980 March-1981 July [?] (Box 7)
  - Campus Unrest (Atlanta, Ga.), 1981 September (Box 7)
  - Canadian Gay Archives (Toronto, Ontario), 1982 July-1986 June [?] (Box 7)
  - Capitol Hill: the Newsletter of the Gay Rights National Lobby (Washington, D.C.), 1979 December [?] (Box 7)
    [Name changed to "News From Capitol Hill"]
  - Caritas Fellowship Newsletter (Beech Island, S.C.), 1987 August-1987 December (Box 7)
  - Carolina Gay Association Newsletter: LAMBDA, 1977 May-1991 October [?] (Box 7)
  - "Cat Chat" (Atlanta, Ga.), 1990 February (Box 7)
  - Cat's Eye (Nashville, Tenn.), 1980 (Box 7)
  - Caution Alert (Atlanta, Ga.), 1983 October-1988 October [?] (Box 7)
  - Celebration '90: Newsletter of Gay Games (Orlando, Fla.), 1989 May (Box 7)
  - Celibate Man, The, 1982 July-1988 October [?] (Box 7)
  - Center Fold, The (Orlando, Fla.), 1990 August (Box 7)
  - Center for Democratic Renewal (Atlanta, Ga.), 1986 February-1991 March [?] (Box 7)
  - Center for Women's Studies and Services Feminist Bulletin (San Diego, Calif.), 1975 December-1978 November (Box 7)
    [Also "The Center Quarterly" 1984 Spring]
  - Changes (Winter Park, Fla.), 1978-1984 (Box 7)
    [Changed from monthly to quarterly in 1982]
  - Changing Horizons (Binghamton, N.Y.), 1990 February-1990 October (Box 7)
  - Changing Men, 1985 (Box 7)
  - Charis Books and More - Newsletter / Catalog (Atlanta, Ga.), 1988-1991 (Box 7)
  - Charlotte Women's Center Newsletter (Charlotte, N.C.), 1975 April-1979 March (Box 7)
  - Chicago Outlines, 1987 June-1988 January (Box 8)
  - Christus Omnibus (Tucson, Ariz.), 1992 August (Box 8)
  - Chrysalis (Los Angeles, Calif.), 1978 June-1980 May [?] (Box 8)
  - Circle, The (Wellington, New Zealand), 1974 October (Box 8)
  - Circuit Rider (Decatur, Ga.), 1978 May-1981 May [?] (Box 8)
  - Citizens Party of Georgia (Atlanta, Ga.), 1980 December-1981 March (Box 8)
  - Citizens Voice (Atlanta, Ga.), 1981 September (Box 8)
  - Civil Liberties - ACLU of Georgia (Atlanta, Ga.), 1986-1989 (Box 8)
  - Civil Rights Digest, 1974-1978 (Box 8)
  - Clearinghouse on Georgia Prisons and Jails, 1978 August-1979 August (Box 8)
  - Clit International, 1985 March (Box 8)
  - Cobb County Group, The, 1990 September (Box 8)
  - Come Out! (New York, N.Y.), 1972 (Box 8)
  - Come Out Fighting, 1976-1982 [?] (Box 8)
  - Come Together, 1972 May (Box 8)
  - Committee on Gay Education (Atlanta, Ga.), 1978 -1978 [?] (Box 8)
    Emory University
  - Committee on Lesbian and Gay History, 1983-1988 [?] (Box 8)
  - Common Ground (Buffalo, N.Y.), 1982 November (Box 8)
    Buffalo State College
  - Common Lives / Lesbian Lives (Iowa City, Iowa), 1981-1988 (Box 8)
  - Common Woman (Winooski, Vt.), 1980 January-1985 May (Box 8)
  - Communiquelles (Montreal, Quebec), 1981-1991 (Box 9)
    [formerly: Bulletin Women's Information and Referral Centre]
  - Communities: Journal of Cooperative Living (Louisa, Va.), 1978 (Box 9)
  - Community Connections (Asheville, N.C.), 1990-1991 (Box 9)
  - Closer: Connections (Asheville, N.C.), 1989 September (Box 9)
  - Compulsive Eating Self-Help Network, 1983 September (Box 9)
  - Concern, 1980-1981 [?] (Box 9)
  - Congregation Tikvah Chadashak (Seattle, Wash.), 1981 May-1981 June (Box 9)
  - Connexions (Oakland, Calif.), 1982-1986 (Box 9)
  - Conscience - Voice of Pro-Choice Catholics, 1985 March-1985 July (Box 9)
  - Convergence (Atlanta, Ga. / Washington, D.C.), 1974 February/March (Box 9)
  - Cornell University: Details on Conference on "Women in Midlife Crises", 1984-1985 (Box 9)
  - Corvallis Wimmins Collective (Curvallis, Ore.), 1981 (Box 9)
  - COSMEP South (Washington, D.C.), 1986 [?] (Box 9)
  - Council on Battered Women (Atlanta, Ga.), 1977 December-1992 (Box 9)
  - Country Bound, 1979 [?] (Box 9)
  - Country Women (Albion, Calif.), 1976-1989 [?] (Box 9)
  - Cowrie - Lesbian / Feminist (New York, N.Y.), 1973 December-1974 April [?] (Box 10)
  - Coyote Howls (San Francisco, Calif.), 1977 (Box 10)
  - Creative Loafing, 1984 January-1983 June (Box 10)
  - Cronicle: Crones Nest Newsletter (Saint Augustine, Fla.), 1985 (Box 10)
  - Crossroads: Newsletter of accessible events of the Deaf and Hearing Gay/Lesbian Community of Atlanta (Decatur, Ga.), 1988 October-1988 November (Box 10)
  - Crossroads: News of the African American Lesbian/Gay Alliance, 1988 August-1990 December (Box 10)
  - Cruise (Atlanta, Ga.), 1983 [?] (Box 10)
  - Dallas Gay Alliance - Dialog, 1989 (Box 10)
  - Dallas News: Iconoclast Comes Out, 1971 or 1972 [?] (Box 10)
  - Dandelion: A Journal of the Movement for a New Society (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1980 [?] (Box 10)
  - DARE - Tennessee Gay and Lesbian News Weekly (Nashville, Tenn.), 1989 (Box 10)
  - Daughters of Sarah: The Magazine for Christian Feminists (Chicago, Ill.), 1988 (Box 10)
  - Dayton Women's Liberation (Dayton, Ohio), 1975 May-1975 October (Box 10)
  - D.C. Area Feminist Alliance (Washington, D.C.), 1978 (Box 10)
  - Demeter (Monterey, Calif.), 1981 April (Box 10)
  - Democratic Party of Georgia, 1979 (Box 10)
  - Deneuve, 1992 (Box 10)
  - Desperate Living (Baltimore, Md.), 1974 (Box 10)
  - Detroit Women's Voice (Ferndale, Mich.), 1982 April-1985 April (Box 10)
  - Diary (Darien, Conn.), 1980 November [?] (Box 10)
  - Dignity (Atlanta, Ga.), 1983-1988 [?] (Box 10)
  - Dinah (Cincinnati, Ohio), 1976 August-1989 July [?] (Box 10)
  - Distaff (New Orleans, La.), 1981-1982 [?] (Box 10)
  - Duchess House Review (Charlotte, N.C.), 1972 (Box 10)
  - Duke - UNC Women's Studies Research Center (Durham, N.C.), 1982-1992 (Box 10)
  - Durham Women's Center Newsletter, The (Durham, N.C.), 1974 March-1978 May [?] (Box 10)
  - Dyke: A Quarterly (New York, N.Y.), 1975-1978 [?] (Box 10)
  - Dyke Digest (Anew Orleans, La.), 1975-1979 [?] (Box 10)
  - Dykes Central News Bulletin (Tampa, Fla.), 1975 April-1975 May (Box 10)
  - Dykes, Disability, and Stuff, dates unknown (Box 10)
  - Echo of Sappho (Brooklyn, N.Y.), 1972-1973 (Box 11)
  - Ecstasy (New York, N.Y.), dates unknown (Box 11)
  - Edge: Education in a Disabled Gay Environment (New York, N.Y.), 1988 (Box 11)
  - Educational Campaign for a Prosperous Georgia, 1984 (Box 11)
  - Emergency Librarian (Toronto, Ontario), 1974 December-1980 April (Box 11)
  - Emma: Pas Magazin Von Frauen Fur Frauen, 1989 May (Box 11)
  - Emory Gay and Lesbian Organisation (Atlanta, Ga.), 1987 February-1991 September [?[ (Box 11)
  - Emory Institute for Women's Studies Newsletter, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Emory Women's Center Newsletter, 1973 (Box 11)
  - Empathy: Newsletter for Professionals Working to End Homophobia, 1988-1989 (Box 11)
  - Empty Closet, The (Rochester, N.Y.), 1980-1983 [?] (Box 11)
  - Enterprising Women (New York, N.Y.), 1979 [?] (Box 11)
  - Equal Defense Alliance (Seattle, Wash.), 1981 March-1983 June (Box 11)
    [missing: 1982]
  - Equal Times (Boston, Mass.), 1980 July [?] (Box 11)
  - ERA Georgia (Atlanta, Ga.), 1979 January-1981 March (Box 11)
  - E.R.I.N. Bulletin (Rooseveltown, N.Y.), 1981 December [?] (Box 11)
  - ETC (ETCETERA) (Atlanta, Ga.), 1990 [?] (Box 11)
  - Evangelical Outreach Ministries, 1978 May-1986 December [?] (Box 11)
  - Every Woman (Los Angeles, Calif.), 1970 July-1972 April (Box 11)
  - Every Woman's Word (Flint, Mich.), 1976 June (Box 11)
  - EWC Update (San Francisco, Calif.), 1981 December-1982 February (Box 11)
  - Examiner: Newsletter of the Tallahassee Feminist Women's Health Center, 1975 January-1976 July [?] (Box 11)
  - Executive Woman, The (New York, N.Y.), 1980 April/May (Box 11)
  - Fag Rag (Boston, Mass.), 1978 [?] (Box 11)
  - Family Next Door, The, 1993 October-1994 March [?] (Box 11)
  - Female Liberation Newsletter (Cambridge, Mass.), dates unknown (Box 11)
  - Female Liberation of Durham-Chapel Hill Newsletter, 1969 August-1971 December (Box 11)
  - Feminary, The (Chapel Hill, N.C.), 1974 October-1982 December (Box 11)
  - Feminine Connections (San Francisco, Calif.), 1986 [?] (Box 12)
  - Feminist, The, 1974 November-1975 April [?] (Box 12)
  - Feminist Action Alliance, 1974 May-1982 November [?] (Box 12)
  - Feminist Art Journal, The, 1973-1975 (Box 12)
  - Feminists for Animal Rights, 1994 (Box 12)
  - Feminist Forum (Tokyo, Japan), 1981 September (Box 12)
  - Feminist Futures International Network (Northampton, Mass.), 1988 (Box 12)
  - Feminist Health Fund (Yellow Spring, Ohio), 1982-1983 (Box 12)
  - Feminist Majority, 1993 March (Box 12)
  - Feminist Media Project Newsletter (Washington, D.C.), 1973 (Box 12)
  - Feminist Newsletter (Durham, N.C.), 1974 January-1974 September (Box 12)
    [formerly: Female Liberation of Durham-Chapel Hill Newsletter]
  - Feminist Publishers News (Palo Alto, Calif.), 1984 Ocober-1987 March [?] (Box 12)
  - Feminist Women's Health Center (Atlanta, Ga.), 1982 June-1992 [?] (Box 12)
  - Feminist Writers' Guild (Berkeley, Calif.), 1978-1984 (Box 12)
    [missing: 1979-1983]
  - Fifth Estate (Detroit, Mich.), 1978 March [?] (Box 12)
  - Fight the Right (New York, N.Y.), 1981 May (Box 12)
  - Fighting Woman News (New York, N.Y.), 1975-1989 (Box 12)
  - Fireweed (Toronto, Ontario), 1980 (Box 12)
  - First City Network - Network News (Savannah, Ga.), 1986 January-1994 April (Box 12)
  - First Tuesday Newsletter, 1978 November (Box 12)
  - Florida Gay Liberation News [Southern Gay Liberator] (Boca Raton, Fla.), 1975 December-1977 June [?] (Box 12)
  - Focus: A Journal for Gay Women Boston Daughters of Biliti's Room (Boston, Mass.), 1973 August-1974 November (Box 12)
  - Focus - Orange County Gay Community Center (Garden Grove, Fla.), 1975 August-1978 January (Box 12)
  - Fountain, 1973 January (Box 12)
  - Fourth Tuesday Forum (Atlanta, Ga.), 1988 July-1994 April (Box 12)
  - Fourth World, The, dates unknown (Box 12)
    [vol.1. no.2 only]
  - FrauenzeiTung (Germany), circa 1975 (Box 12)
  - Free Dessie Woods, 1977 September-1978 July (Box 12)
  - The Freedom Socialist: Voice of Revolutionary Feminism (Seattle, Wash.), 1991 February-1991 November (Box 12)
  - Friendly Woman (Chicago, Ill.), 1980 November [?] (Box 12)
  - Friends (Atlanta, Ga.), 1985 December-1986 May [?] (Box 12)
  - Fritt Fram (Oslo, Norway), 1987 April (Box 12)
  - From Now On (Montgomery, Ala.), 1975 March-1977 February (Box 13)
  - Frontiers: A Journal of Women Studies, 1979-1980 (Box 13)
  - Front Page (Indiana), 1973 September-1973 October (Box 13)
  - Front Page, The (Raleigh, N.C.), circa 1983 (Box 13)
  - Full Moon (Northampton, Mass.), 1972 March [?] (Box 13)
  - Fund Focus: The Fund for Human Dignity, 1987 Winter (Box 13)